♪Looking in the mirror,
my temples have turned white♪
♪Taking off the hairpins and makeup,
shedding the disguise♪
♪A cold face♪
♪With two lines of tears♪
♪If an actor could gain pity♪
♪The audience offers sincere words♪
♪Perhaps the story could be changed♪
♪The storyteller says♪
♪This mortal world is full of turmoil♪
♪Within sight but beyond reach♪
♪Yet I still don't want to give up♪
♪Don't let the memory be hollowed out♪
♪Don't make me ridiculous♪
♪Some vows turn into smoke
and fade away♪
♪Even the leaves know when autumn comes,
but you don't even know me♪
♪Imprisoned in plight,
yet still full of passion♪
♪I mock this absurd and entangled love♪
♪How can I bear to let go♪
=Whispers of Southern Song=
=Episode 13=
Miss Jiang.
Miss Jiang, are you all right?
I wanted to ask you something,
but you left in a hurry.
Luckily I followed you.
None of your business.
I know you still resent me.
I don't expect you to forgive me,
but I don't want you to be hurt again.
Do you know this person?
Judging from his tattoo,
he must be from Xiaosheng Society.
It isn't safe here.
Let's talk later.
The person in this photo is my mother.
How did you get this photo?
The kingfisher phoenix crown
your mother was wearing in the photo,
do you know where it is now?
You haven't answered my question yet.
Forget it.
It seems you still want to deceive me.
I found this photo
among Master's old belongings.
My mother passed away very early.
Are you saying
that Head Rong knew my mother?
Then this person in the photo
is Head Rong?
At that time,
Master should still
be called Zhao Shengge.
Are you saying that Head Rong
was the murderer of Xu You'an's mother?
No way.
Master would never
be a villain who took lives.
Something must be hidden
about what happened eight years ago.
Does Xu You'an know?
No way.
I need to go tell Xu You'an.
Miss Jiang,
we must not let him know
until the matter is clarified.
You know his temperament.
I won't hide it from him with you.
Because I know how terrible
the feeling of being deceived is.
I'm not trying to deceive him.
Once I find out the truth,
I will tell him everything.
With the kingfisher phoenix crown,
perhaps I can see the truth back then.
Rong Xiaonan, why did you deceive me?
Xu You'an, calm down.
Master would never
commit such a heinous crime.
I will dig out all the truth.
The case from eight years ago
has solid evidence.
He faked his death to escape punishment.
What are you defending him for?
Give me some time.
Once I find out the truth,
proving that he truly did wrong,
then I shall
atone for his sins.
Atone for his sins?
You reminded me.
Then you shall atone for his sins.
If you doubt me,
then you can shoot me
to death right now.
You made it sound reasonable.
But the truth you mentioned
is nothing but an excuse
to clear your master.
Since you want an explanation,
okay then.
Now kneel down to atone
and apologize to me.
I said kneel!
Kneel!
Xu You'an.
Xu You'an, calm down.
Calm down.
I won't cooperate with someone
as selfish and disgusting as you.
From now on,
my matters with Chun'er
are none of your business.
Now get out of the Governor Mansion!
The kingfisher phoenix crown
is in the hidden compartment
of my father's room.
You saved me.
I repay this to you.
From now on, we are even.
I didn't expect
you would come to this day.
Mr. Du, why mock me?
Since you are here,
you must come for a cooperation.
Why not get to the point?
Get to the point?
Cooperation?
If it weren't for the fact
that I haven't obtained the items,
I would blow up
your Governor Mansion right now
and send you and your son to death.
How about we cooperate
and send Xu You'an to death?
Then the previous deal can continue.
You are now like a fish
waiting to be slaughtered.
Why would I cooperate with you?
The phoenix crown
is in the Jiang residence.
We can discuss cooperation
after you get the crown.
This is my sincerity.
Okay.
Who are you?
Search this place thoroughly
to find the phoenix crown!
- Yes!
This...
(Rongqing Troupe)
Kill him!
Move aside!
What are you doing?
Stop!
He is that scum's disciple!
Zhao Shengge is dead.
We can kill him to seek revenge.
Kill him!
(How did they know
that Master is Zhao Shengge?)
Kill him!
Wait!
Killing him would be too lenient.
Since you want us
to spare the Rongqing Troupe,
why not sing a piece for us?
If you please us all,
we'll spare you. How about it?
- Sing a piece!
What do you mean?
You can't sing without makeup?
Fine.
I'll help you then.
I'll help you.
Beat him to death!
You lowly performer!
Governor is here.
Let's go.
Governor has left.
Beat him!
I wonder who leaked the news.
Governor,
are we really going
to leave Rong Xiaonan alone?
Beat him to death!
You lowly performer!
He deserves to die!
Let's go.
By the way,
a servant from the Jiang family said
that the Xiaosheng Society sent people
to make a scene in the Jiang residence.
Do we send someone to check?
Does the Xiaosheng Society know
the crown is in the Jiang residence?
To the Jiang residence.
(Rongqing Troupe)
(Peerless Beauty And Grace)
(Only by first clarifying the truth,)
(can I find a way
to prove Master's innocence.)
Why did you mistakenly abduct
the sister of a military officer?
Now they are conducting
a massive search,
we can't keep these goods.
We need to think of a way
to cover it up,
otherwise, trouble will come to us.
Zhao Shengge just came to us.
And your Madam Gu knows too much.
She can't be left alive.
Rest assured.
I've already taken care of her.
Xu Fan and President Jiang are culprits
of the murder case back then.
♪As if it were fate♪
♪Deliberately playing tricks♪
♪We miss each other♪
♪Creating a turbulent drama♪
♪And a bizarre♪
♪Anonymous legend♪
♪The plot twists and turns♪
♪Play out over and over again♪
♪Waiting to be discarded♪
♪And you are like a moth to the flame♪
♪Refuse to submit♪
♪I can't bear to blame you♪
♪There are always too many♪
♪Helpless situations♪
♪Overwhelmed by time♪
♪Even if I have questions♪
♪I harbor desires♪
♪Nowhere to find answers♪
♪People come and go♪
♪I'm still all alone♪
♪Wandering around♪
♪Fortunate to have you with me♪
♪Go through the entanglement♪
♪If longing♪
♪Turns into dust and smoke♪
♪How can I be at ease♪
♪Having walked through prosperous times♪
♪And travelled around the world♪
♪Scars all over me♪
♪If longing never fades♪
♪Burns still hot♪
♪Let it turn into dust and smoke♪
♪After half a lifetime of loneliness♪
♪In the next life♪
♪Entangle with you again♪